(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-14T23:02:28.910365",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
倍の倍のFight 倍倍Fight by CANDY TUNE
Double the double Fight, double Fight by CANDY TUNE!
本音と建前 ない私
A me without true feelings or social pretenses...
なりたい ありたい けど だけど…
...is what I want to be, but, well...
人の目気にせず素直な子
An honest girl unbothered by what others think...
なりたい ありたい けど だけど…
...is what I want to be, but, well...
誰かを救うということは 過去の自分も救うことです
Saving someone means saving your past self, too.
誰かを愛すということは 本当の自分を大好きになることです
Loving someone means coming to love your true self.
倍Fight 倍倍Fight 倍倍倍Fight
Double Fight! Double double Fight! Double double double Fight!
何回転んでも立ち上がれ
No matter how many times you fall, stand right back up!
倍Fight 倍倍Fight 倍倍倍Fight
Double Fight! Double double Fight! Double double double Fight!
厄介な問題も飛び越えろ
Leap over even the most troublesome problems!
嬉しい＝倍倍倍倍
Happy = double double double double!
悲しい＝bye bye bye bye
Sad = bye bye bye bye!
ほら倍の倍のバイのバイでもっと行こうよ
Come on, let's go even further at double, quadruple the pace!
倍Fight 倍倍Fight 倍倍倍Fight
Double Fight! Double double Fight! Double double double Fight!
飽き性 根気ない状況
Easily bored, lacking perseverance...
やめたい やめたい けど だけど…
...I want to quit that, I really do, but...
もっぱらネガティブ自虐思考
Always trapped in negative, self-deprecating thoughts...
やめたい やめたい けど だけど…
...I want to quit that, I really do, but...
何かを犠牲にすることは 何かを目指すということです
Sacrificing something means aiming for something greater.
何かを目指すということは 何かを本気で信じるということです
Aiming for something means truly believing in something.
倍Fight 倍倍Fight 倍倍倍Fight
Double Fight! Double double Fight! Double double double Fight!
なんてまあ素敵なこの人生
What a truly wonderful life this is!
倍Fight 倍倍Fight 倍倍倍Fight
Double Fight! Double double Fight! Double double double Fight!
だって私はそう私だもん
'Cause after all, I'm just me!
楽しい＝倍倍倍倍
Fun = double double double double!
悔しい＝bye bye bye bye
Frustration = bye bye bye bye!
ほら倍の倍のバイのバイでもっと行こうよ
Come on, let's go even further at double, quadruple the pace!
倍Fight 倍倍Fight 倍倍倍Fight
Double Fight! Double double Fight! Double double double Fight!
倍の倍のFight 倍倍Fight by CANDY TUNE
Double the double Fight, double Fight by CANDY TUNE!
自分を大事に 本音を大事に 躓いたって (倍々FIGHT!)
Value yourself, value your true feelings—even if you stumble! (Double Fight!)
強い人間になりたかったって？ 今からなれるさ (倍々FIGHT!)
You wanted to become strong? You can start right now! (Double Fight!)
有言実行 言葉に宿った魂信じて (倍々FIGHT!)
Walk the talk, believe in the soul within your words! (Double Fight!)
誰かと比べて落ち込んだって 自分は自分さ (倍々FIGHT!)
Even if comparing yourself to others gets you down, you are you! (Double Fight!)
半径100km 幸せで満たしたいな (倍々FIGHT!)
I want to fill a 100 km radius with happiness! (Double Fight!)
生きているだけで凄いことだから 命を褒めよう (倍々FIGHT!)
Just being alive is amazing, so praise life! (Double Fight!)
できないことよりできること ほら数えてみようよ (倍々FIGHT!)
Count what you can do rather than what you can't! (Double Fight!)
すなわちとにかく倍々アクティブ…
In other words, stay doubly active...
ばしのバイバイファイ！
...bai-bai fight!
バイバイバイ ほんの小さな一歩
Bye-bye-bye, just a tiny little step,
バイバイバイ 大きな大きな一歩
Bye-bye-bye, a big, big step,
バイバイバイ どれも君にとって
Bye-bye-bye, whichever it is, to you,
大切さ 大切な勇気の証だよ
it's precious, a precious proof of your courage!
バイファイ ババファイ バババイファイ
Bai-fight, ba-ba-fight, ba-ba-bai-fight!
何と言われても諦めぬ
No matter what anyone says, don't give up!
バイファイ バイバイファイ バイバイバイファイ
Bai-fight, bai-bai-fight, bai-bai-bai-fight!
人生これきり一度きり
You only get one life, just this once!
バイファイ ババファイ バババイファイ
Bai-fight, ba-ba-fight, ba-ba-bai-fight!
何回転んでも立ち上がれ
No matter how many times you fall, get back up!
バイファイ ババファイ バババイファイ
Bai-fight, ba-ba-fight, ba-ba-bai-fight!
厄介な問題も飛び越えろ
Leap over even the most troublesome problems!
嬉しい
So happy!
楽しい
So fun!
ほら倍の倍の倍の倍で持って行こうよ
Come on, let's take it double of double of double!
バイファイ バイバイファイ バイバイバイファイ
Bai-fight, bai-bai-fight, bai-bai-bai-fight!
せーのーで
Ready, set,
晴れ時々大正解！
Sunny with a chance of absolute success!
険しい道も共に歩んだ
We walked down steep, rugged roads together,
You will never walk alone
躓いてもがいて強くなるんだ
Stumbling and struggling is how we grow stronger!
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
険しい道も共に歩んだ
We walked down steep, rugged roads together,
You will never walk alone
躓いてもがいて強くなるんだ
Stumbling and struggling is how we grow stronger!
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
明日からじゃなくて今日だ今だ君だここだ
Not tomorrow—it's today, it's now, it's you, right here!
背負いこんで疲れたならちょっと休むかい
If you're tired from carrying it all, wanna rest a bit?
私たちがいつもそばにいるからさ
Because we'll always be by your side!
バイファイ バイファイ バイファイ！
Bai-fight, bai-fight, bai-fight!
はーい！君たち～！
Hey there, everyone~!
4周年記念ライブ、始まりましたね～！
The 4th Anniversary Live has officially begun~!
ハッシュタグは、えー、こちら！こちら！こちら！
The hashtag is, uh, right here! Here! Here!
宝鐘マリン4周年3Dライブになっておりますー！
It's #宝鐘マリン4周年3DLIVE!
この後ね、知ってるとは思うけど、んー、水着のお披露目が
After this, as I'm sure you already know, mm, we'll have...
ありますので。3D水着、うー！楽しみでしょう？！
...the swimsuit reveal! 3D swimsuits! Ooh, excited, aren't you?!
いっぱいスクショして、ツイートしてくださ... ポスト！
Take tons of screenshots and tweet... I mean, post them!
ポストしてください！
Please post them!
ここから先も、まだまだ、えー、素敵なゲストの皆さん来ますので、
From here on, we still have wonderful guests coming up,
一体どんな曲、どんなパフォーマンスをするのか、超超楽しみに！
so look forward to what songs and performances we'll do!
そして水着もどんな感じなのか、差分もいっぱいあるからね。
And see what the swimsuits look like—there are lots of variations, too!
あの、差分も全部見切ってから、見切ってくださいね！
So make sure you check out all of them, okay?!
そして素敵な、うん、グッズもね、マリンがいっぱい考えたグッズとかもありますんで、
Also, there's wonderful merch that Marine put lots of thought into,
さあ、どんどん楽しんでいきましょー！
so let's keep having a blast!
行くぞー！
Here we go~!
ロンリー・ローリー・神降臨
Lonely loli god descent!
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Ring the bell, and just like that,
これが救済のレクイエム
this is a requiem of salvation!
せーの！
Ready, go!
触ったら逮捕！
Touch me and you're arrested!
極中で点呼！
Roll call in prison!
1 2 3 4！
1, 2, 3, 4!
ごめんなさーい！
I'm so sorry!
あー、ごめんなさいが聞こえなーい！
Ah, I can't hear your apology!
えーっ？！
What?!
粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム
Purifying Saint!! Loli God Requiem!
触らないわ
I won't touch you.
お前なんかに好かれたくない
I don't want someone like you liking me.
泥水で口を洗え
Go wash your mouth out with muddy water.
ほうら、手ぇ出せ
Come on, put out your hands.
さあ、おまわりさん連れて行って
Come on, officer, take me away!
妄想しか取り柄のない
A pitiful person whose only redeeming quality...
かわいそうな人
...is having delusions.
（ういちゃん、ういちゃん、待ってよういちゃん）
(Ui-chan, Ui-chan, wait for me, Ui-chan!)
その姿、親に見せられますか？
Can you show that state of yours to your parents?
（ういちゃん、マリンちゃんかわいいよー）
(Ui-chan, Marine-chan is cute too~)
あ、ありがと。お疲れ様です。
Ah, thank you. Thanks for your hard work.
ロリ・ロリ・神降臨
Loli-loli god descent!
マジやばいやつランドセル
That school backpack on a total creep!
パトカーの邪魔にならないよう
So you don't get in the police car's way,
早く消えてください
please disappear right now!
ラブリー・ロリ・ロリ・神降臨
Lovely loli-loli god descent!
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Ring the bell, and just like that,
とっても優しくて素敵なオニイチャン
a super kind and wonderful big brother...
ラフエンド...ほら、
rough end... look,
なーんちゃって
just kidding!
ほら、世の中にはこんなに淫らな大人たちがはびこっているのです
Look, the world is crawling with so many depraved adults!
みんな晒しあげますよ！
I'm going to expose you all!
準備して！
Get ready!
触ったら逮捕！
Touch me and you're arrested!
極中で点呼！
Roll call in prison!
1 2 3 4！
1, 2, 3, 4!
ごめんなさーい！
I'm so sorry!
あー、ごめんなさいが聞こえなーい！
Ah, I can't hear your apology!
えーっ？！
What?!
粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム
Purifying Saint!! Loli God Requiem!
はーい！獄中にいるみなさーん！
Hello, everyone in prison~!
刑務所ファンミーティングのお時間でーす！
It's time for the prison fan meeting~!
その腐りきった耳をゴリゴリかっぽじって、
Clean out those completely rotten ears of yours...
よーく聞いてくださいね！
...and listen very carefully!
雑魚♡
Small fry♡
キモキモ...
Gross, gross...
助かるぅ
That hits the spot~
うるさい
Shut up!
助かるぅ
That hits the spot~
黙ってもらっていいですか？
Could you please be quiet?
助かるぅ
That hits the spot~
嫌いです
I hate you.
助かるぅ
That hits the spot~
かわいそう
So pathetic.
助かるぅ
That hits the spot~
だーさっ
So lame~
よーわっ
So weak~
みっともなっ
So unsightly~
どうしようもない お兄ちゃん お姉ちゃん
Hopeless big brothers, big sisters,
もう希望もない ゴミだ おめーら
you have no hope left, you're all trash!
汚物消毒110番
Filth disinfection, dial 110!
固有結界 は・つ・ど・う♡
Reality Marble: Ac-ti-vate♡
粛聖！ういビーム！
Purification! Ui Beam!
ああああー！
Aaaahhh~!
もういっちょ！
One more time!
ういビーム！
Ui Beam!
ああああー！
Aaaahhh~!
まだまだぁ！
Not done yet!
ういビーム！
Ui Beam!
怒りの日
Day of wrath...
聖なるインターネットに 血の雨が降り注いだ日
The day a rain of blood poured down on the sacred internet...
愚かなロリコンを 骨の髄まで浄化する一筋の光
A single ray of light purifying foolish lolicons down to the marrow...
それが、ういビームなのだ
That is the Ui Beam.
ういは、すべてを赦します
Ui forgives everything...
嗚呼 この世の醜さを 集めて描いてみるよ
Ah, gathering the ugliness of this world, I'll try to draw it.
真っ白なキャンバスが 汚れて泣いている
The pure white canvas is defiled and crying.
lonely 振り向いた少女は そっと手を掴む
Lonely, the girl who turned around softly grabs your hand.
『楽園など 無いから』
"Because there is no paradise."
おっきなお友達のみんなへ
To all our big friends,
お前らが打ち込んでいる虚無には 何の意味があるの？
what meaning is there in the void you're typing into?
ねぇ、教えてよ。マリン、
Hey, tell me. Marine...
ぜんぜーんわかんないんだ！
doesn't understand at all!
ロリ ロリ神、降臨
Loli-loli goddess, descends,
さよなら 笑顔でバイバイ
say goodbye with a smile, bye-bye!
ピリオドをどうぞ
Please take a period,
この手で押してあげる
I'll put an end to it with my own hands!
Lovely ロリ ロリ神、降臨
Lovely loli-loli goddess, descends!
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
If you ring the bell, this is the way.
とても優しくて 素敵なお兄ちゃん
Such a very gentle and wonderful big brother,
楽園で ほら ねんねしな
now go to sleep in paradise.
それが救済の レクイエム
That is the requiem of salvation.
せーのっ
Ready, set...
触ったら逮捕
Touch me and you're arrested!
極”chu-de”点呼
Extreme roll call with a kiss!
いち にー さん しー？ ごめんなさーい
One, two, three, four? "We're sorry!"
はぁ？ごめんなさいが聞こえない
Huh? I couldn't hear your apology!
粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム☆
Purification!! Loli-Kami Requiem☆
ほんっとーに、気持ち悪い
Reaaally, you guys are disgusting.
マリンちゃん7周年おめでとう。じゃ、帰るね
Marine-chan, happy 7th anniversary. Well, I'm heading home.
ちょ、待って！
Wait, hold on!
巻き起こすぜ
Let's make some waves,
航海！
on this voyage!
行きますよー！
Here we go~!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Pretty girls are innocent!
マリン！マリン！マリン！
Marine! Marine! Marine!
もう一回！
One more time!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Pretty girls are innocent!
うい！うい！ういは無罪！
Ui! Ui! Ui is innocent!
ねえ 言ったよね？ 年齢なんて関係ないってさ
Hey, you said it, right? That age doesn't matter,
そういうめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれるって
that you'd love me even with all my troublesome flaws!
ねえ ねえ 言ったよね？
Hey, hey, you said it, right?
言ってない？
You didn't?
あ、そういうこと言うんだ。ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
Ah, so that's how it is. By the way, "Pretty Girl Innocence" applies on this ship!
任せて 魔法で若返り
Leave it to me, I'll turn young with magic!
秘密の姿は今だけ
This secret look is for right now only...
特別ですよー
It's very special~!
嗚呼 あたしゃ可愛いや
Ah, I'm just so cute!
湊となんかじゃ 収まらない我が力
My power cannot be contained by a mere harbor!
宝の島に着いてほしい気分
Feeling like arriving at a treasure island!
ちょっとお節介 邪魔かい？
Is being a little meddlesome a nuisance?
君の一番でいさせてよ そら
Let me be your number one, look!
本当は自信ないけど 頑張っちゃう
I'm not really confident, but I'll do my best!
キュッキュッキュルン
Kyu-kyu-kyurun!
恋する気持ち 17歳
In love at heart, forever 17!
てっぺんに立つわ 大人の時間
I'll stand at the top! It's grown-up time!
ドキドキしてる？
Is your heart pounding?
まだ早い
Too early for that!
だ・だ・だめですか？フリルの服着たら
Is... is it no good if I wear frilly clothes?
そんなことないよ
Not at all!
だ・だ・だって魔法少女になってみたい
B-B-Because I wanna try being a magical girl!
ギリギリ有罪
Barely guilty!
粛清！
Purge!
えーっ！？
What!?
なんちゃって するから見捨てないで君たち
Just kidding! I'll do anything, so don't abandon me, guys!
ちょっといいとこ見てみたい
I wanna see you shine a bit!
嗚呼 たまにいじけてさ
Ah, sometimes I sulk,
嗚呼 それでもいいの
ah, but that's fine too!
年頃だもん 本気にしちゃう
It's that age, after all, I take it seriously!
嵐の真ん中 一緒に行こう
Into the midst of the storm, let's go together!
ハートにチャーム 美少女無罪
Charming your heart, pretty girls are innocent!
あれ あれ どうした？
Oh my, oh my, what's wrong?
面倒くさいよなんて言っちゃって
Saying "you're such a pain",
構ってくれる 君が好き
yet you still pay attention to me—I love you!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun, kyu-kyu-kyurunrun!
優しくしてね 17歳
Please be gentle with this 17-year-old.
突っ込んで 経験値 お楽しみ chu♡
Dive right in, gain some experience, and enjoy, chu♡
ドキドキして ルージュ？
Are you flustered over my rouge?
あぁ…お許しくださ～い！
Ah... please forgive me~!
このういの 魅力！魔力！不可抗力！
This Ui's charm! Magic! Irresistibility!
──”罪な女”ね？
—Quite a sinful woman, aren't I?
離さないで つかまっていて
Don't let go, hold on tight!
世界の広さ 見せてあげるから！
Because I'll show you how big the world is!
（出航ー！！）
(Set sail!!)
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, pretty girls are not guilty!
キミの一番 目指して ヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one, steady as she goes!
冗談も大好きだけど 真剣よ
I love joking around, but I'm being serious!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun, kyu-kyu-kyurunrun!
恋する気持ち 17歳
Loving feelings, sweet 17!
てっぺんになっちゃうわ オトナの時間
It's about to hit midnight, grown-up time!
ドキドキして ルージュ？
Heart racing over my rouge?
まだ早い♡
It's still too early♡
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！マリン！マリン！マリンは...
Not guilty! Not guilty! Pretty girl is not guilty! Marine! Marine! Marine is...
まだだよ！
Not yet!
もう一回！無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！うい！うい！ういは無罪！
One more time! Not guilty! Not guilty! Pretty girl is not guilty! Ui! Ui! Ui is not guilty!
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ
Sparkling as ever, dizzying even more!
マリン船長とういちゃんだろぉぉぉう！！
It's Captain Marine and Ui-chan, got it?!
はぁー！
Haa~!
まりんちゃーん！
Marine-chaaan!
あー、ういちゃーん！
Ah, Ui-chaaan!
ということで、マリンズは...
And so, the Marines are...
疲れてる...
You're exhausted...
ですから。さすが9歳、元気いっぱいね。
I am. As expected of a 9-year-old, full of energy.
えー？ちょっと無理してる。
Eh? I'm pushing myself a bit.
はい、マリンの急所...あ、違った。
Yes, Marine's critical... ah, wrong word.
お前も9歳ではない！
You're not 9 years old either!
そうです！なんと7周年ライブにちゃんとういちゃんが来てくれましたー！
That's right! For my 7th anniversary live, Ui-chan came to join us!
イエーイ！お邪魔しまーす！おめでとーう！
Yay! Thanks for having me! Congratulations!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
なんとね、マリンね、16歳のういとはね...
You know, Marine and 16-year-old Ui are...
うん。／まあ、もうめっちゃマブ？
Yeah. / Well, practically besties, right?
あ、そうなんだー。
Ah, is that so?
なんだけどね、ういちゃんともね、これからマブになっていきたいなって思ってて、初絡みなんですけど。
But you know, I wanted to become besties with Ui-chan from now on, even though this is our first collab.
うん。／どうぞ、よろしく。
Yeah. / Pleased to meet you.
あ、帰りまーす。
Ah, I'm heading home.
ちょっと！ちょ、待てよ！ちょ待てよ！ちょ待てよ！ちょ、待てよ。
Wait! Hey, wait up! Wait up! Wait up! Hey, wait up.
ということでね。／はーい！
Anyway! / Yaaay!
はい、ういちゃん、何か気付かない？
Yes, Ui-chan, notice anything?
え？露出？
Eh? The skin exposure?
あ、すごい、あ、すごい。／お、あ、興味ある？興味ある？
Oh, wow, oh wow. / Oh, are you interested? Interested?
これね、ういちゃん、あなたの放ったういビームで…バァン！
You see, Ui-chan, your Ui Beam hit me and... BAM!
あの、新しい設定つけるのやめてくださーい。
Um, please stop adding new lore.
ういビームで服が弾け飛んだ。／飛んだ？
My clothes got blown off by the Ui Beam. / Blown off?
そんなこんなありましてね、新衣装となっております。
And with all that, this is my new outfit!
めっちゃ可愛...え、なんかぬいぐるみ付いてる！
Super cute... wait, there are plushies attached!
あ、そうなの！付いてるの！
Ah, yes! There are!
欲しい！1個もらっていい？
I want one! Can I have one?
うわ、すごい9歳っぽい！めっちゃきゅー...あ、いいよ！いいよ、あげようね。
Whoa, that sounds so 9-year-old! So cu— ah, sure! Sure, I'll give you one.
いや、ブチッ！おっぱいもげる、ブチッ！
Wait, *rip*! My boob's gonna tear off, *rip*!
お土産！じゃあねー！／ちょ、待てよ！
A souvenir! Bye now~! / Hey, wait up!
ちょ待てよ！ちょ待てよ！見て、ほら、ここにさ。ほら、3...
Wait up! Wait up! Look, right here. See, 3...
3...／あ、本当だ！背中に3...
3... / Ah, it's true! A 3 on your back...
ほら、お尻透け...
Look, see-through butt...
30じゃないよ！
It's not 30!
3年！30じゃないよ！
3rd anniversary! Not 30!
いや、ういちゃんね、これね、まだまだ脱げるんで。
You know, Ui-chan, I can take off even more with this.
大丈夫ですか？
Are you sure that's okay?
このあとね、これから...／BANされますよ？大丈夫ですか？
After this, from now on... / You'll get banned, you know? Is that okay?
髪型とか、服とか、まだまだね、違うのがあるのね。
The hairstyle, clothes, and more, there are still different versions.
みんなね、これで満足して帰らないように。
So everyone, don't just be satisfied with this and leave!
あの、カバーさん、頑張って隠してください。
Um, COVER Corporation, please do your best to censor her.
まだあるよ、まだまだあるよ！ということで、えっとね、選曲の話もね、しようと思うんですけど。
There's more, so much more! So anyway, I wanted to talk about our song choices too.
うん。／えーっと、ういとは...あ、違う、ういちゃん。ういちゃんとは...
Yeah. / Um, with Ui... ah, no, Ui-chan. With Ui-chan...
ええ、やっぱりね、持ち歌の『粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム☆』やりましたけど、かわちぃ！
Naturally, we performed her original song "Shukusei!! Loli-Kami Requiem☆", and it was so cute!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
えっとね、マリン歌ってみたも出してるんですけど。
Well, Marine also released a "Sang It" cover of it...
球体のやつね。
The spherical one, right.
そう、マリンの歌ってみたのバージョンだと、めっちゃ「れっくえええむ！！」って感じで歌ってたんだけど。
Yeah, in Marine's cover version, I sang it like "REQUIEEEEEM!!"
なんて？
What?
「れっくえええむ！！」って感じで、グッてひねり出してたんだけど。
"REQUIEEEEEM!!" like that, squeezing it out with full force.
ま、今回はね、もうなんかマリンもこの姿のまま「れっくえええむ！！」って言ったら、ちょっと「あっ」てなるから。
Well, this time, if Marine shouted "REQUIEEEEEM!!" in this outfit, it'd be a bit awkward...
言ってるね、もう今ね。
You just said it right now though.
ここはちょっと真面目にね、普通にいつものマリンで歌わせていただきました。
So here, I sang it seriously, just as normal Marine.
そっちのほうがいいよ。よしよし、マリンちゃん。
That's much better. Good girl, Marine-chan.
なんだよ、なんだよ。／オカズ作りしない方がいいよ。
What's with that? / You shouldn't be making material for that.
なんでや！やめろ！
Why not?! Stop that!
あとは、あの、ういの方とはね、Kアリーナでういのライブで一緒に歌わせてもらった...
Also, with Ui, we sang together at Ui's live at K-Arena...
やってたねー！／歌いましたので。
We did that! / Since we sang that before.
疲れた。
I'm tired.
疲れた。疲れたね。いいよ、もう帰って。疲れたでしょ。
Tired. You're tired, huh. It's fine, go ahead home. You must be tired.
じゃ、帰ります。／話終わったから。
Well, I'm heading off. / Since our talk is over.
まだまだライブは続くぞー！
The live concert is still going on!
冷たい...
So cold...
まだまだ続くー！レッツゴー！
It's still continuing! Let's go!
冷たい...／お、置いてった。
So cold... / Oh, she left.
こんなに求められてないことある？
Has anyone ever been so unneeded?
パレ パレ パレ
Parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
We're gonna shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
With the voices calling out as our cue!
パレ パレ パレ
Parade, parade, parade!
探しにゆく
We're going to search
スタートは何度だって
Starting over time and time again!
手を掲げて
Raise your hands!
Clap your hands
海の向こうまで
All the way across the sea
Clap your hands
届きますように
So it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら 一緒に everybody
Come on, everybody together!
Clap your hands
空の向こうまで
All the way across the sky
Clap your hands
響きますように
So it echoes
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す 僕たちの未来
Shining light on our future!
Are you ready?
コン コン コン
Kon, kon, kon!
Yes こんな狐に化かされて
Yes, bewitched by a fox like this
Knock, knock, knock
心を開けて
Open up your heart
Everything's gonna be alrightって感じよ
Feel like everything's gonna be alright
今、噂の bewitch you
Right now, we'll bewitch you like they say
もう一回
One more time!
コン コン コン
Kon, kon, kon!
Yes こんな狐に化かされて
Yes, bewitched by a fox like this
Knock, knock, knock
心を開けて
Open up your heart
Don't stop music!
ほら 朝まで行くよ
Come on, we'll go till morning!
今、地球の裏にチューニング
Now tuning to the other side of the Earth
コン コン コン 魔法をかけて
Kon, kon, kon, casting a spell
飽きるまで be with you
Be with you until you've had enough!
ねぇ もっと好きになってもらいたいの
Hey, I want you to love me even more!
頭の中は君ばっか！
My head is filled only with you!
そっぽなんて向いてないで
Don't you look away from me
あぁもう ヤキモチしちゃうわ あぁ
Ah, you're making me so jealous, ah!
ずっと ずっと 好きがいいの
I want you to love me forever and ever
心の奥もときめいちゃうくらいに
So much that the depths of my heart flutter
こっち向いててよ ねぇダーリン？
Look this way, won't you, darling?
あぁもう 離さないから 絶対に
Ah, I won't let you go, definitely!
Love you, love you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I love you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
あぁ
Ah...
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って drivin'
Jump into the cheeky carriage and go drivin'
あたしは大大変身メイクアップ！
I get a super makeover, make-up!
我儘のまにまに 燦きに注意
As selfish as I want, beware the sparkle
洒落た街で dancin'
Dancin' in the stylish town
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
Farewell, goodbye inferiority complex
何時かは喝采 クラップ・オーディエンス
Someday, cheers, clap audience!
皆々御唱和あれ！
Everyone, sing along!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo-wa, Bibbidi-bobbidi-boowa, yeah
混線がっても仕様が無い ガラスシューズで踊る tonight
No helping if lines cross, dance in glass shoes tonight
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo-wa, Bibbidi-bobbidi-boowa, yeah
今夜に明日など無い
There is no tomorrow tonight
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
So whoever dances freely wins, right?
失礼しますが死んでください！
Pardon me, but please DIE!
Kill 'em with the bass
殺す事が楽しい
Killing is so much fun
Teehee, bitch
Murder is so fucking 可愛い
Murder is so fucking cute
可愛い、ね
Cute, right?
死神先生 Calliope
Reaper Sensei Calliope
Kill 'em with the bass, 'til we get 'em to say:
Alright, "Yay! 素敵な暗殺〜," so it goes
Alright, "Yay! What a lovely assassination~," so it goes
Dead Beats listen up, it's what you wanted, me callin' up in the night to ya
勝手にやってる 地獄で犯罪じゃないから
Doing as we like, 'cause in Hell it isn't a crime
It's all up to you, scream or make a sound
We dance anyway cuz it's human nature
今更もうなんとなく 一緒に楽しもう
At this point, might as well enjoy it together
あなたの死ぬ日は
On the day that you die...
申し訳ないです、やり過ぎました！なんでケツでラップしてる？ちょっと変だ？
I'm sorry, I overdid it! Why am I rapping with my butt? A bit weird?
一切合切任され Doggy doggy god
Leave everything to me, doggy doggy god
Oh yeah!
You can goodbye bye bye baby Doggy doggy god
当然今日のシップ 堂々 Doggy doggy god
Naturally today's ship, proudly doggy doggy god
Oh yeah!
Clap your hands, wag your tail, on and on and on
Bow-wow-wow! Louder than words ありのままさ
Bow-wow-wow! Louder than words, just as you are
ワンワンワン ダー ダーダー フルの この生き様
Wan-wan-wan da-da-da, this all-out way of life
掴んだら 離さない One chanceで 輝く
Once grabbed, never let go, shining in one chance
ひゃっほー！
Hya-hoo!
I'm a 絶対的 霊験あらたかな Doggy god
I'm an absolute, miraculously divine doggy god
ああ 混沌 情報過多のレストランで
Ah, in a restaurant overflowing with chaotic info
嘘っぱちのメニューにお茶こぼして
Spilling tea all over the phony menu
君と もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu mogu mogu with you
銃撃戦の真ん中で もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu in the middle of a firefight
うぎゃ〜
Ugyaa~
魑魅魍魎 ハラペコの群れ
A ravenous horde of evil spirits
満腹になる未来を願っているよ
Wishing for a future where everyone's full
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu mogu mogu
世界が終わる前に
Before the world comes to an end
もぐもぐ yummy マジ神
Mogu mogu yummy, totally divine
ヤムヤム ありのまんま
Yum yum, just as we are
もぐもぐ yummy magic coming
Mogu mogu yummy magic coming
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Let's savor this world, yum yum
Sexy 世界一 Super ピチピチ
World's #1 sexy, super youthful and fresh!
Sexy 世界一 Super ピチピチ ぶっちゃけ船長捕まえたくない？
The sexiest in the world, super youthful and fresh—frankly, don't you want to capture the Captain?
You're gonna get the treasure Maybe tasting me
私の甘さが欲しいでしょ
You want my sweetness, don't you?
(Ah-hoy! Da-ba-da-boi. Ah-hoy!)
秘宝の鍵を
Take the key to the treasure...
(Ah-hoy! Da-ba-da-boi. Ah-hoy!)
優しく刺して
and gently insert it...
(Ah-hoy! Da-ba-da-boi. Ah-hoy!)
宝庫の扉
into the vault's door.
ああ ああ ああ ああ
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
マジで早く開けて！
Seriously, open it already!
Ahoy
自覚無いでしょうね
You probably don't even realize...
思い通りに
that you're being moved...
君は動かされている事
exactly as intended.
単純じゃないの
It isn't so simple...
駆け引きの糸を
the strings of our tactical game.
すべて見失って
Losing sight of everything,
唯一無二のジョーカー手にする事で
and holding the one and only Joker in hand...
理解できた
Even the shape of love...
愛の形も
that we finally understood...
どこかの誰かに仕組まれていて
was all orchestrated by someone, somewhere.
偽って舞おう 最後に笑うQueen
Let us dance in disguise, as the Queen who laughs last.
加速していく
It's accelerating—
(Be in a love, be in a love)
捨て身の鼓動
this reckless heartbeat.
(Be in a love, be in a love)
全滅ぎりのステージへ
Towards a stage on the brink of total annihilation!
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my dreams,
らしく輝きたい
I want to shine as my true self!
時に涙して
Shedding tears at times,
また笑い合いたい
I want to share laughter once again.
同じ未来を見たい
I want to look toward the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream!
踏み出そう 奇跡の一歩を
Let's take that miraculous first step!
息切らして 夢追いかけたい
Out of breath, I want to chase after our dreams!
ワクワク止まらない
This excitement just won't stop!
想像超えてく
Beyond imagination,
世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a whole new world!
アクセスしてみたい？
Don't you want to log on?
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here!
それぞれ違う
With our different,
違った
different
心で
hearts,
作るworld
we create our world!
はい 注目〜！
Alright, eyes on us!
一聴でノックアウト
Knocked out in just one listen,
Shit, thank you, 散々なのは
shit, thank you, being terrible is—
Ah ah ah
あれ？君たちの声、まだ足りてないんじゃないの〜？
Huh? Your voices still aren't loud enough, are they?
Alright, just begun. Ayy, blast blast it
赤く火照るbody
This flushed, burning body...
瞳潤んじゃってるって
Look, your eyes are already moistening.
乾いた喉潤すオアシス染まり
Quenching a dry throat, soaked in an oasis...
Ah heh
たまらないんだろう？
You can't get enough of it, can you?
Hot from shore to shore, I'm gonna get your ass on the dance floor
We taking over LA, Miami, New York
Step to the rhythm and you ready for more
You wanna block my shine, block that you somehow
I can make it rain when I hit the tempo, baby
Get ready if you wanna ride on waves all day
落ちた涙は誰？
Whose fallen tears are those?
目差し上げた苗
A seedling that sprouted...
揺らいじゃうような
It seems so fragile,
熱さ足りない
the heat is still lacking!
Alright, just begun. Ayy, blast blast it
弾けて派手に垂れ
Bursting open and spilling lavishly,
果てまで身を伸ぼれ
drown yourself in it all the way to the end.
All eyes on me, I can take you higher
Ayy, まだまだ沸いていこうぜ
Ayy, let's keep hyping it up even more!
はい 注目〜！
Alright, eyes on us!
一聴でノックアウト
Knocked out in just one listen,
Shit, thank you, 散々なのは
shit, thank you, being terrible is—
Ah ah ah
Freeze!
Look at that chicks got that yum, now let me just bounce with it all the night
¿Qué pasa? Quiero colorado taco, set spicy, give me a holler, die
Watch low, what's good, look at me, cool and be cool, look at there, tell to me, eye
To pop and be inside, fry, coloring forever stuck purity
Bring in the heat that could blow this place away
Dripping a bit, catching sight on all eyes and proud I'm just chilling
Pour some champagne I'm sipping, 'cause I can't let you lose
Now pack and let you have a taste
この体で
With this body...
Let me rock your body
着こなす肌に
On this flawless skin...
Step with ya, step with ya...
Light up bonfire, alluring smoke fades to haze
Blast, blast it
We'll drive you crazy
熱く 苦しくなってこぼした
Growing hot and breathless, I let it spill...
One night, my bright spotlight
どんどん新境地行っちゃいそう？
Ready to enter a whole new world?
アーツチチな二人はだぁれ？
Who are these two hot girls? (Yeah, baby)
Hands up ぶち上げた前！
Hands up, put 'em high! (Oh, baby)
クラッときちゃうような
Like you're feeling dizzy,
熱が足りない
the heat isn't enough yet.
Our night's just begun
Ay, let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Burst out and go wild in style! (Yeah, baby)
来世まで we wanna party
We wanna party till the next life (Oh, baby)
All eyes on me
I can taste the high
Ay まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
Ay, keep the excitement rising!
はーい注目
Hey, attention!
まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Shall we dance together once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは…
Stealing the spotlight is...
Bring it back, let's hit it one last time
はーい注目
Hey, attention!
まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Shall we dance together once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは…
Stealing the spotlight is...
i-i-i
あれ？君たちの声、まだ足りてないんじゃないのー？
Huh? Aren't your voices still not loud enough?
Our night's just begun
Ay, let's blast it!
赤く火照る face
Red-flushed face
ヒートアップしちゃって絡む sweat
Heating up, intertwining sweat
渇いた喉潤す
Moistening a dry throat
オアシスよ マリンブルー
An oasis, marine blue
あっはーん！
Ah-ha-an!
たまらないんでしょ？
You can't resist it, right?
From shore to shore, I'm gonna get your ass on the dance floor
We taking over LA, MIA, New York
Step to the rhythm, and you ready for more
Don't wanna block my shine, don't get yourself blocked
I can make it rain when I hit the jackpot, baby
Get ready if you wanna ride on waves all day!
アーツチチな二人はだぁれ？
Who are these two hot girls? (Yeah, baby)
Hands up ぶち上げた前！
Hands up, put 'em high! (Oh, baby)
クラッときちゃうような
Like you're feeling dizzy,
熱が足りない
the heat isn't enough yet.
Our night's just begun
Ay, let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Burst out and go wild in style! (Yeah, baby)
来世まで we wanna party
We wanna party till the next life (Oh, baby)
All eyes on me
I can taste the high
Ay まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
Ay, keep the excitement rising!
はーい注目
Hey, attention!
まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Shall we dance together once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは…
Stealing the spotlight is...
i-i-i
Hey! 進化したギャング 海賊船動くぞ Alright
Hey! The evolved gang, the pirate ship is moving, alright!
キャプテン航路どっか コサックダンス 客席見渡す
Captain navigating somewhere, Cossack dance, looking out at the crowd
よそ見すんな こっち見ろ こっち見ろ こっち見て こっち見て こっち見ろ！
Don't look away! Look here, look here, look at me, look at me, look here!
スーパーフロウ ビキニ 17歳 からの永遠の17歳 Ah~
Super flow, bikini, 17 years old, and forever 17 years old, ah~
Bring in the heat that can't be splashed away
Fishing a big catch, the stardom I deserve, but I'm just chilling
A mocktail Mai Tai, sipping
'Cause I got that juice
Might let you have a taste
この身体で
With this body,
Let me rock your body
気配残す肌に
Leaving traces on the skin
Now rock that, yeah, ah
Side of bonfire, alluring smoke takes you high
Ahoy! We drive you crazy
Crazy...
Ahoy! 熱苦しくなってこう
Ahoy! Let's get hot and heavy!
もうどうしようもない
There's no stopping us now
One night, my bright spotlight
どんどん新境地行っちゃいそう？
Ready to enter a whole new world?
アーツチチな二人はだぁれ？
Who are these two hot girls? (Yeah, baby)
Hands up ぶち上げた前！
Hands up, put 'em high! (Oh, baby)
クラッときちゃうような
Like you're feeling dizzy,
熱が足りない
the heat isn't enough yet.
Our night's just begun
Ay, let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Burst out and go wild in style! (Yeah, baby)
来世まで we wanna party
We wanna party till the next life (Oh, baby)
All eyes on me
I can taste the high
Ay まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
Ay, keep the excitement rising!
はーい注目
Hey, attention!
まあいっちょ踊ってこうか？
Shall we dance together once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは…
Stealing the spotlight is...
Bring it back, let's hit it one last time
これラストラッシュ、手加減なし、世界最強じゃん？
This is the final rush, no holding back, aren't we the strongest in the world?
Just two besties so fly
Ah-ah-ah
[Title: IRIS OUT]
Ah, ah, ah...
だめ だめ だめ 脳みその中から
No, no, no, from deep inside my brain,
「やめろ馬鹿」と叫くモラリティ
morality screams, "Stop it, you idiot!"
ダーリン、ベイビー、i、ダーリン
Darling, baby, I, darling,
半端なくラブ！とキラキラ浮き足立つフィロソフィ
a philosophy of head-over-heels, sparkling love!
死ぬほど 可愛い上目遣い
So cute it kills me, that upward glance,
何がし方に 触れるくらい
just about touching, somehow.
ばらまく乱心 気づけば当人
Scattering madness, before I realize it,
この世に生まれてきた君が悪い
it's your fault for being born into this world.
やたらと しんどい恋わずらい
Painfully exhausting, lovesickness,
バラバラなる頭とこの身体
my shattered head and this body,
頸動脈からアイラブユーが噴き出て
blowing a spray of "I love you" from my carotid artery...
IRIS OUT
一体どうしよう この想いを
What on earth should I do with these feelings?
どうしよう あばらの中を
What should I do deep inside my ribs?
ザラメが溶けてゲロになりそう
Rock sugar is melting, feels like I'm gonna puke,
瞳孔バチ開いて溺れ死にそう
pupils wide open, feels like I'm gonna drown to death.
今この世で君だけ大正解
In this world right now, only you are the right answer!
誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？
Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who?
ひっくり返しても価値のない 君だけのルールは適用外
Even flipped over, it has no value; your rules don't apply here!
いっそ燃やすか？ 殺すしかない？ 勝つわけ放題
Should I just burn it? Must I kill it? Free to win however I want!
君が笑顔で放った アバダケダブラで心神喪失 申し訳ねえな
Lost my mind from the Avada Kedavra you shot with a smile—sorry about that!
やり直させて
Let me do it over!
爪抜いて
Pull out my nails!
ここじゃなくて
Not here!
死ぬほど可愛いお前のマネーじゃ 何がし骨に障るくらい
Your insanely cute imitation just rubs me the wrong way!
頭クラクラし 気づけば当然 この世に生まれた君が悪い
My head spins, and naturally, it's your fault for being born into this world!
パチモンでもいい 何でもいい 今君となついてる全て欲しい
A knockoff is fine, anything goes! I want everything that clings to you now!
頸動脈からアイラブユーを吹き出せ
Spurt out "I love you" straight from your carotid artery!
あ、あ、あ、アイリスアウト
Ah, ah, ah, IRIS OUT!
一体どうしよう この想い落とそう
What on earth should I do? Let's drop these feelings.
油膜の向こう
Beyond the oil slick...
ゾロ目が溶けてゲロになりそう
Matching dice melting, about to turn into vomit!
さあ怒号
Come on, roar!
バチ開いて こぼれ散りそう
Spread wide, about to spill and scatter!
今この世で君だけ大正解
In this world right now, only you are the right answer!
誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？ 誰？
Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who? Who?
らーーー！
Raaaa!
やったー！ こぼー！
Yay! Kobo!
おめでとー！
Congratulations!
ありがとう、こぼー！
Thank you, Kobo!
イエーー！ Happy anniversary!
Yay! Happy anniversary!
おー、そうそうそう！
Oh, right, right, right!
かわちい、かわちい！ はい！
So cute, so cute! Yes!
ちょっと服似てるよ、ほら。ね、似てるね？
Our outfits kinda match, look! Right? They match!
うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah.
似てる？ / 似てるよー！
Do they? / They do!
似てる。ほら、ふー... あ、これフード。
They match. Look, hoo... ah, this is a hood.
どう？ / フード。
How is it? / A hood.
こぼもフードありますよ。
Kobo has a hood too!
え？ / これ。 / どれ？ どこや？
Huh? / This. / Which one? Where?
埋まってる！
It's buried!
被れないだろ、それ！
You can't even put that on!
うわー、かわちいねー。
Wow, it's so cute.
え、どう？ どこが可愛い？ どこが？
How is it? What part is cute? Where?
めっちゃセクシーのなんか... oh, swimsuit!
It's super sexy, like... oh, swimsuit!
あ、そう、swimsuit!
Ah, right, swimsuit!
ああー、セクシー！ 水着可愛いよ！
Aah, sexy! The swimsuit is cute!
こぼもこのswimsuit欲しい！ / 欲しい？
Kobo wants this swimsuit too! / You do?
うん、なんかこぼは... / うん。
Yeah, Kobo is like... / Yeah.
リボン好き！
I like ribbons!
リボン？ うん、どのリボン？
Ribbons? Yeah, which ribbon?
この... いや、見た... ああー！
This... no, look... aah!
リボンはこれ！ / これ？
The ribbon is this one! / This one?
うーん、ちっちゃいけど...
Yeah, it's small though...
あ、これ？ ちっちゃリボン、ちっちゃリボン。
Ah, this? Little ribbon, little ribbon.
うん。あ、見た？ / あ、見た。見た見た。
Yeah. Ah, did you see it? / Ah, I saw it. I saw, I saw.
あんた... / 綺麗！
You... / Beautiful!
ああ、すごい。
Ah, amazing.
あ、こっちも！ / あ、こっちも？
Ah, here too! / Ah, here too?
ああ、そうそうそう、これ。
Ah, yes, yes, yes, this!
めっちゃ可愛い！ このリボンが...
Super cute! This ribbon is...
うわあー！ ああー！
Uwaaa! Aaa!
待って、リボンとお尻どっちが可愛い？
Wait, which is cuter, the ribbon or my butt?
もっと、もっとセクシー、もっと... / あ、もっと？
More, more sexy, more... / Ah, more?
えい！ えい！ / おお！ えい！
Take that! Take that! / Oh! Take that!
ああー！ うわあー！
Aaa! Uwaaa!
助かる！
Thank you for the treat!
え、こぼもっとさあ、脱いでるの見たいでしょ？
Kobo, you want to see me take off more, right?
はい！ あ...
Yes! Ah...
あの、これ、パッ、パッ...
Like, take this off, off...
え、ダメだよー！
Eh, no way!
ダメ？ ま、いっか。脱いでくる！
No? Well, whatever. I'm gonna go take it off!
え？ え？ / 見せてあげる、こぼ。
Eh? Eh? / I'll show you, Kobo.
だ、大丈夫ですか？ え？ 大丈夫ですか？
A-Are you sure about this? Eh? Is it okay?
楽しみに待ってて。
Look forward to it.
大丈夫ですか？ え？ いや...
Are you sure? Eh? No...
見て。
Look.
いやー！ やっべー！ やっべー！
Nooo! Oh crap! Oh crap!
こぼ、見て。 / やっべー！
Kobo, look. / Oh crap!
こぼ、見て。
Kobo, look.
Wow! Wow! Wow sexy lady!
Woah! Chill!
もういい、もういい。服着るわ、服着る。
Alright, alright. I'll put my clothes on.
やっべー！
Oh crap!
うん。BANされないようにね。
Yeah, so we don't get banned.
やっべー！ 子供ー！ 子供見... 子供、no, don't look!
Oh crap! Kids! Kids, look... Kids, no, don't look!
あ、もう着た、もう着た。ほら、じゃーん！
Ah, I'm dressed already. Look, ta-da!
ああー！ すごい！
Aah! Amazing!
大丈夫！ / これセーフ、セーフ！
It's all good! / This is safe, safe!
セーフ！
Safe!
はい、すごーい！
Yes, awesome!
で、今日はね、あの「III」のね...
And today, we had "III"...
はい！ そう！ そう！
Yes! Right! Right!
楽しかったー！ / 楽しかった！
That was so fun! / So fun!
マリン、お尻...
Marine, your butt...
あ、ねー！
Ah, right!
And I like... today "III" is ... Senna version!
And I like... today, "III" is the Senna version!
そう！ そうなの！ すっごいかっこいいバージョンに歌わせてもらって...
Yes! Exactly! We got to sing such a cool version...
カバーさせてもらいました。かっこいいバージョンありがとうございます！
We got to do this cover. Thank you so much for the cool version!
Great job with the cover, damn!
マリンの英語のラップどうだった？
How was Marine's English rap?
She got the gyatt! No, let me see you work with all of that!
She got the gyatt!
Gyatt! Get!
Yeah! No, let me see you work with all of that!
うまっ！
You're so good!
いやいやいや...
No, no, no...
Come on, come on! / No, let me see you work with all of that!
って何？ あん？
What does that mean? Huh?
続きますので ぜひ見ていってください〜
It will continue, so please be sure to keep watching!
こぼありがと〜 / ありがと〜
Thanks, Kobo! / Thank you!
いや〜〜〜ん
Noooo!
わ〜〜〜い
Yayyy!
乗って... あ、重っ！
Climbing on... Ah, you're heavy!
うわあああああ、重い！
Waaaaah, you're heavy!
重いよ〜！
So heavy!
死んだ...
I'm dead...
死んだ / 死んだ...
Dead. / Dead...
お別れしたのはもっと 前の事だったような
It feels like our parting happened a long time ago.
悲しい光は封じ込めて 踵すり減らしたんだ
I sealed away that sad light and wore down the heels of my shoes.
君といた時は見えた 今は見えなくなった
What I could see when I was with you has now disappeared from view,
透明な彗星をぼんやりと でもそれだけ探している
yet I still vaguely search for that invisible comet, and nothing else.
しょっちゅう唄を歌ったよ その時だけのメロディーを
I often sang songs, melodies made just for that fleeting moment.
寂しくなんかなかったよ ちゃんと寂しくなれたから
I wasn't lonely at all, because I was truly able to feel loneliness.
いつまでどこまでなんて 正常か異常かなんて
Wondering how long or how far, whether it's normal or abnormal—
考える暇も無い程 歩くのは大変だ
walking is so tough that I don't even have time to think about it.
楽しい方がずっといいよ ごまかして笑っていくよ
Having fun is so much better; I'll just brush it off with a laugh.
大丈夫だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消えやしない
It's alright, even if I forget that pain, it will never disappear.
理想で作った道を 現実が塗り替えてくよ
Reality paints over the path built out of ideals.
思い出はその軌跡の上で 輝きになって残ってる
Our memories remain as a radiant glow upon that trail.
お別れしたのは何で 何のためだったんだろうな
I wonder why we parted, and what it was all for.
悲しい光が僕の影を 前に長く伸ばしている
The sorrowful light casts my shadow far ahead of me.
時々熱が出るよ
Sometimes I come down with a fever,
時間がある時眠るよ
and whenever I have time, I sleep.
夢だと解るその中で 君と会ってからまた行こう
Inside that dream where I know it's a dream, I'll meet you before moving on again.
晴天とはほど遠い 終わらない暗闇にも
Even in this endless darkness, so far from clear skies,
星を思い浮かべたなら すぐ銀河の中だ
if I picture a star in my mind, I'm instantly inside the galaxy.
あまり泣かなくなっても 靴を新しくしても
Even if I don't cry much anymore, even if I get brand-new shoes,
大丈夫だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消えやしない
it's alright, even if I forget that pain, it will never disappear.
伝えたかった事が きっとあったんだろうな
There must have been something I wanted to tell you.
恐らくありきたりなんだろうけど こんなにも
It's probably something ordinary, but even so...
お別れした事は 出会った事と繋がっている
Saying goodbye is connected to having met you in the first place.
あの透明な彗星は 透明だから無くならない
That invisible comet will never disappear, precisely because it is invisible.
○×△どれかなんて 皆と比べてどうか吉凶なんて
Right, wrong, or somewhere in between; how I compare to everyone else, good fortune or bad—
確かめる間も無い程 生きるのは最高だ
living is so wonderful that I don't even have time to check.
あまり泣かなくなっても ごまかして笑っていくよ
Even if I don't cry much anymore, I'll just brush it off with a laugh.
大丈夫だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消えやしない
It's alright, even if I forget that pain, it will never disappear.
大丈夫だ あの光の 始まりには
It's alright, because at the very beginning of that light...
君がいる
...you are there.
朝起きて 今日は何しよう
Waking up in the morning, what should I do today?
好奇心を抑えらんない
I can't hold back my curiosity!
踊り出すハートは 制御不可能
My dancing heart is uncontrollable!
テンプレは丸めて捨てて
Crumple up the templates and throw them away,
スキップで踏んづけちゃおう
let's stomp all over them with a skip!
地球全部塗り替えちゃおう
Let's repaint the entire earth!
ガチコチはだるいし まじ無理！
Being all stiff is such a drag, seriously no way!
そんなんソッコーイチ抜け！
I'm ditching that immediately!
あっかんべーなんだが
Sticking my tongue out at it,
上等！
bring it on!
心拍数上げて生きようよ
Let's live with our heart rates pumped up!
退屈奪っていこうよ
Let's strip away all the boredom!
ウザいのも沼って
Even get obsessed with what's annoying,
好きになっちゃうよ☆
and you'll fall in love with it☆
完璧キャラ無理ゲー知らんぷり
Playing a perfect character is impossible, just play dumb!
可愛すぎちゃってグランプリ
Overwhelmingly cute, winning the Grand Prix!
Ah 何でも知りたい味見したい
Ah, I want to know everything, I want a taste!
誰も止められやしない
Nobody can stop me!
歌わずにはいられない
I just can't help but sing!
もしもで諦めるより
Rather than giving up on "what-ifs,"
もしもでBETかましたい
I'd rather place a bet on "what-if"!
こんな世界 知らない方が損じゃん？
Missing out on a world like this would be such a waste, right?
疲れたらちょっとサボって
When you're tired, slack off a bit,
糖分で回復して
recharge with some sugar,
自分のご機嫌取ろう
and keep yourself in good spirits!
優等生演じてても無理！
Pretending to be an honor student is impossible!
ナチュラルで愛らしい乙女なんだが
I'm just naturally an adorable maiden,
最強！
invincible!
大好き囲まれて生きようよ
Let's live surrounded by everything we love!
明日も笑っていたいよ
I want to be smiling tomorrow, too!
知っちゃったら
Once you know it,
そのまま好きになっちゃうぜ☆
you'll fall right in love with it☆
妄想キャパ無限 上げてく視界
Endless capacity for delusions, broadening my horizons!
頂上にだって連れてくし
I'll even take you all the way to the top!
Ah いつでも無茶振り 攻めの姿勢
Ah, always making unreasonable demands, keeping an aggressive stance!
誰も止められやしない
Nobody can stop me!
踊らずにはいられない
I just can't help but dance!
下向いているそこの君
Hey you over there, looking down!
不満ばかり零しても意味ないじゃんバカ！
Spilling nothing but complaints is pointless, dummy!
リセットは無し一度きり
There are no resets, you only get one shot!
いつでも真剣勝負ギリギリ
Always a serious match right on the edge!
もっともっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more, more!
ワガママになろうぜ！君の人生☆
Let's be selfish! It's your life☆
我慢とかしなくていい
You don't have to hold back!
そばにいる
I'm right by your side!
今もこれからもずっと
Now and forever from here on,
約束！
I promise!
心拍数上げて生きようよ
Let's live with our heart rates pumped up!
退屈奪っていこうよ
Let's strip away all the boredom!
ウザいのも沼って
Even get obsessed with what's annoying,
好きになっちゃうよ☆
and you'll fall in love with it☆
完璧キャラ無理ゲー知らんぷり
Playing a perfect character is impossible, just play dumb!
可愛すぎちゃってグランプリ
Overwhelmingly cute, winning the Grand Prix!
Ah 何でも知りたい味見したい
Ah, I want to know everything, I want a taste!
誰も止められやしない
Nobody can stop me!
歌わずにはいられない
I just can't help but sing!
コンプレックスプリンセス♡
Complex Princess♡
La La La La La La La
一瞬記憶が錯乱するが、恋は恋だ。
For an instant my memory is confused, but love is love.
お楽しみボディ
A body made for pleasure
愛のボランティア 撫でます！ ドンッ！！
A volunteer of love, I'll caress you! Boom!!
どす恋 患い
Deeply lovesick
圧倒的な 母性と
With overwhelming maternal affection
（キミたちがー♡）
(You all are-♡)
勝手に進む 年齢
Age marches on uncontrollably
（止められねぇんだよ！）
(You can't stop it!)
鳴らない 鐘を 鳴らしましょう
Let's ring the bell that doesn't ring
私だけを 見てくれますか？
Will you look only at me?
ねぇ♡
Hey♡
好き 好き 好き 好き 片思い
Love, love, love, love, unrequited love
めちゃ めちゃ めちゃ めちゃ 描いたフューチャー
A future envisioned so, so, so, so much
大事に 大事にして ダーリン
Cherish, cherish me, darling
コンプレックスプリンセス
Complex Princess
宜しくお願いします♡♡♡♡
Please take good care of me♡♡♡♡
コンプレックスプリンセス♡
Complex Princess♡
La La La La La La La
コンプレックスプリンセス♡
Complex Princess♡
La La La La La La La
SEXY & CUTE 全部見せたい 今会いたい♡
SEXY & CUTE, I want to show you everything, I want to see you now♡
（ようこそ！ マリンワールドへ！！）
(Welcome to Marine World!!)
運命共同体 一心同体 側にいたい♡
Tied by destiny, one in body and soul, I want to be by your side♡
（流石に寂しいわ！ 愛されたい！！）
(Naturally, I'm lonely! I want to be loved!!)
恋愛 不器用 まである
I'm even clumsy at romance
（脈なしボンバー）
(Hopeless bomber)
ぶっちゃけ 嫉妬の 申し子
Honestly, the very embodiment of jealousy
（膝から崩れ落ちる）
(Collapsing to my knees)
ずっと17歳 もっと愛しなさい
Forever 17, love me even more
夢が大きくて ごめんなさい！
Sorry for having such big dreams!
ホラ♡
Look♡
好き 好き 好き 好き 気付いて
Love, love, love, love, notice me
てぇてぇ絆を 思い出して
Remember our precious bond
熱々 圧力 女子力
Burning hot, high-pressure girl power
自己肯定低い お姫様♡
A princess with low self-esteem♡
お迎えに来て 王子様♡
Come sweep me away, Prince Charming♡
Ah～ 時には ヘラる時も あるけど
Ah~ Though there are times I get emotionally wrecked,
シナジー全開 海より深い 恋心 認知して！
with full synergy, please acknowledge this love deeper than the sea!
（聞こえておりますでしょうかー！？）
(Can you hear me out there!?)
Ahoy!
ヨーソロー！
Steady as she goes!
出航！！
Set sail!!
ねーえー♡
Heyyy♡
好き 好き 好き 好き 片思い
Love, love, love, love, unrequited love
めちゃ めちゃ めちゃ めちゃ 描いたフューチャー
A future envisioned so, so, so, so much
大事に 大事にして ダーリン
Cherish, cherish me, darling
コンプレックスプリンセス
Complex Princess
キミを幸せにします♡♡♡♡
I'll make you happy♡♡♡♡
コンプリートプリンセス♡
Complete Princess♡
恋する乙女
A maiden in love
コンプリートプリンセス♡
Complete Princess♡
生まれ変わるの
I will be reborn
キミのプリンセス♡
As your princess♡
というわけで、なんと！
And so, amazingly!
ツクヨミで大人気の神楽さんに来ていただきましたー！
We have the super popular Kagura-san from Tsukuyomi here!
イエーイ！神楽だよ！神楽だよー！
Yay! It's Kagura! It's Kagura~!
うわーー！かわいいーー！えへへ、かわいいですね！
Waaah! So cute! Ehehe, isn't she cute!
めっちゃかわいい！
Super cute!
かわいいです！イェーイ！
She's cute! Yay!
ま、ところでですね、
Well, by the way,
うん。
Yeah.
初絡みなので、
since this is our first time interacting,
うん。
Yeah.
え、お互いの呼び方とか決めたいんですけど。
um, I'd like to decide what we call each other.
おー、ちょっちょっちょっと、ねぇ、
Oh, wait, wait, wait, hey...
かぐやはー、
Kaguya is...
はい！
Yes!
「かぐや」で？
"Kaguya"?
あ、「かぐや」で。そうですねー。
Ah, as "Kaguya". That's right~
うん。
Yeah.
え、じゃあマリンのことは、ま、マリンでもいいし船長でもいいんですけど、ま、なんでもオッケーで！
Um, so for me, Marine is fine, or Senchou is fine, anything's okay!
じゃあー、
Then...
え？
Huh?
「マリン」って呼ぶね！
I'll call you "Marine"!
ぐっ！くらった！
Guh! Critical hit!
呼ぶね！
I'll call you that!
超かわいい！
Super cute!
えー！
Ehee!
きゃー！かわいい！
Kyaa! Cute!
うふふふ！
Ufufufu!
あー最高だ。
Ah, the best.
ね、マリン今日呼んでくれてありがとう！
Hey, Marine, thanks for inviting me today!
ありがとうございますー！
Thank you so much~!
ね、すごいよ、こんな大きくて素敵なステージで歌えてさ！
It's amazing getting to sing on such a huge, wonderful stage!
うん！
Yeah!
もうテンションも爆上げって感じ超楽しかった！
My hype was totally maxed out, it was super fun!
あーよかったですー！
Ah, I'm so glad~!
でさ、
And you know,
うん。
Yeah.
マリンは活動7周年なんだよね？
it's your 7th anniversary of activities, right?
そうなんです！
That's right!
おめでと！
Congrats!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much~!
おめでと！
Congrats!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
おめでとおめでと！いや、7年ですよ、7年！
Congrats, congrats! Man, 7 years, 7 years!
すっげー！
Incredible!
いや、神楽まだまだ新人だと思うんですけど、
Well, I think Kagura is still very much a newcomer, but...
ててて！
No no no!
ちょっとね、神楽も末永く、7年、いやそれを超える勢いで！
I want Kagura to go for a long time too—7 years, no, even beyond that!
おっ！
Oh!
末永く活動してください！
Please keep going for a long time!
当たり前じゃん！一生やるぞ！
Of course! I'll do this forever!
あ、一生やってくれ神楽！やれやれー！
Ah, do it for life, Kagura! Go, go!
マリンと神楽一生やるぞ！
Marine and Kagura will do this for life!
やるぞーー！
Let's do it~!
行くぞ！行くぞマリン！行くぞ！行くぞ！
Let's go! Let's go Marine! Let's go! Let's go!
エイ、エイ、オーーー！
Ei, ei, ohhhh!
どういうテンションなの？
What kind of vibe is this?
はははは！
Hahaha!
マリンはね、このカグヤの感情豊かなね、歌声が大好きで！
Marine just loves your emotionally expressive singing voice, Kaguya!
歌唱力が高いだけじゃなく、表現まで凄いし。
Not only are you a great singer, but your expressiveness is incredible too.
ねー！本当に元気の出る曲でした！楽しかったです！
Right?! It was such an energizing song! It was so much fun!
えー嬉しい！カグヤ、もう超アガった！
Yay, I'm so happy! It was super hype, Kaguya!
ね、お互いのオリ曲を一緒に披露したわけなんですけど、
Yeah! We performed each other's original songs together,
マリンの『コンプレックス・プリンセス』歌ってみてどうでしたか？
but how was it singing Marine's "Complex Princess"?
えー、もうめちゃ楽しかったー！
Oh, it was so much fun!
おー、よかったー！
Oh, I'm so glad!
もう歌もダンスも可愛いしさ、
The song and dance are both super cute,
あとコーレスもめちゃくちゃ楽しい！
and the call-and-response is super fun too!
楽しい～
So fun~
もうみんなと一体になれる感じがさ、本当にプリンセスにふさわしい曲だったよね！
That feeling of becoming one with everyone made it truly a song fit for a princess!
あーそうそう！プリンセスですから！最高やねん！
Ah, right, right! Because we're princesses! The best!
Wプリンセスですよ、私たち。
We're double princesses, the two of us.
そうなんですよ。
That's right.
もう本当に可愛い！もう一生推します！
You're really so cute! I'll simp for you forever!
きゅん！
Kyun!
あー、可愛すぎる！
Ah, way too cute!
最後にカグヤから何かマリンのチャンネルの視聴者に向けてのメッセージや告知などありますでしょうか？
Lastly, Kaguya, do you have any message or announcements for the viewers on Marine's channel?
はい、ございまーす！
Yes, I do!
みんなー！マリンとカグヤのコラボステージを見てくれて本当にありがとうー！
Everyone! Thank you all so much for watching Marine and Kaguya's collab stage!
カグヤ、すっごく楽しかったよー！
Kaguya had so much fun!
次はツクヨミにも遊びに来てね！
Come hang out at Tsukuyomi next time too!
来てー！
Please come!
そして、カグヤも出てる映画『超・かぐや姫！』が9月18日金曜日から4DXなどの特別フォーマットにパワーアップして上映されることが決定したよ！
Also, the movie featuring Kaguya, "Chou Kaguya-hime!", will be screened in enhanced special formats like 4DX starting Friday, September 18th!
おー！新衣装！どう、似合う？可愛い！
Ooh! A new outfit! How is it, does it suit me? So cute!
そうなの！新衣装で撮影したムビチケも売ってるから、みんな絶対買ってね！
That's right! Movie tickets featuring the new outfit are on sale, so make sure to get yours!
えー、買わなきゃ！買わなきゃ、イェイイェイ！
Ah, gotta buy it! Gotta buy it, yay yay!
そして、12月にツクヨミ感謝祭っていうイベントでライブやるんだー！
And in December, I'll be performing live at an event called Tsukuyomi Kanshasai!
ライブキタ！ワクワクするっしょ！するするー！
A live show! Exciting, right?! Totally!
みんな絶対楽しいから来てね！よろしくー！
It'll definitely be fun, so please come, everyone! Looking forward to it!
いやー、キタこれー！
Woo, this is awesome!
今日のステージを見て、みんなカグヤのパフォーマンスにメロメロになったと思うんで、もっと見たいっていう方は要チェックとなっております！
Seeing today's stage, I'm sure everyone fell head over heels for Kaguya's performance, so if you want to see more, definitely check it out!
マリンもね、カグヤの魅力にはぁ…メロメロですよ、本当に。
Marine is also... *sigh*... totally head over heels for your charm, Kaguya. Truly.
メロメロでちゅかー？
Are you head over heels~?
あー、メロメロでちゅー。
Ah, head over heels~
メロメロビーム！あー、メロメロ～
Melomelo Beam! Ahh, head over heels~
食らってるー！
It hit you!
でもね、メロメロはメロメロでも、マリンのメロメロはカグヤを娘にしたいっていう、そういうメロメロだから。
But wait, even though I'm enamored, Marine's kind of enamored means wanting you as my daughter!
えー、何ー？娘ー？娘にしたいけど。
Ehh, what? Daughter? I do want you as my daughter, though.
えー、娘にしたがるー。欲しがるよ、娘。イロピーが恨めしいなー。
Ehh, always wanting a daughter~ Of course I want a daughter! I'm so jealous of Iro-P~
そうだ、イロピーに怒られちゃう。
That's right, Iro-P will get mad at you.
そうだよ、怒られちゃうね。イロピーのものですから我慢します。
That's right, I'll get scolded. You belong to Iro-P, so I'll hold back.
いや本当に今度は是非マリンもツクヨミに呼んでください！
Really, please invite Marine to Tsukuyomi next time!
えー、もう絶対来てよ！絶対面白いよ！行きたーい！
Oh, definitely come! It'll definitely be fun! I wanna go!
で、マリン、また一緒にライブしようね！絶対です！本当にしたい！
And Marine, let's do a live show together again! Absolutely! I really want to!
本当に今日は来てくれてありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much for coming today!
こちらこそありがとー！ありがとうー。
Thank YOU so much! Thank you~
じゃあまたねー！バイバーイ！バイバーイ！
See you later! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
特報
[Special Announcement]
まるでバーバレラ メロメロよ
Just like Barbarella, I'm madly in love
かなりモーレツにピチピチよん
Quite fiercely in the prime of youth
でもサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
But Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday, solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ Mine
I love it all, I love it all, I love it all, mine
あ もうムリ 終わり 鬱 全然かわいくないしさ
Ah, no more, it's over, depression. I'm not cute at all, and...
めんどーくさいよね？ はー消えたい 消えよ
I'm such a hassle, right? *Sigh* I wanna disappear. I will.
え？ そこがいい！ ウソばっか
Eh? That's what's great! Total lies.
いい女！ 本当に？
Fine woman! Really?
お宝以上！！！ そうかな～
Better than treasure!!! You think so~?
最後のヒロイン そうかにゃあ？
The ultimate heroine! Is that so, meow?
弱気バイバイ スタコラサッサ
Timidity bye-bye, scurrying away!
そそそそうかもね そうだよね！
Y-Y-Y-Yeah, maybe so! That's right!
にゃーんか元気になってきた！
Sometheeeng's got me feeling energized!
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday, solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ Mine
I love it all, I love it all, I love it all, mine
私が瞬く度 鳴り響くSE
Every time I blink, sound effects echo
きゃぴ
Kyapi♡
新曲MV このあとプレミア公開
[New Song MV Premiere Right After This]
洗脳したげる 洗脳したげる
I'll brainwash you, I'll brainwash you
I'm a leader, you're not a leader. Forever seventeen! Be sexy!
もっとアイドルでいさせてよ
Let me be an idol a little longer!
(ヤバパヤパ Shake it! Shake it!)
(Yabapayapa, shake it! Shake it!)
ぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃぎゃ……きゃぴ
Gya-gya-gya-gya-gya-gya-gya-gya... kyapi♡
(1 & 2 & 3 & 4 Shake it! Shake it!)
(1 & 2 & 3 & 4)
きゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅ……きゅるん
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu... kyurun♡
まるでバーバレラ メロメロよ
Just like Barbarella, I'm madly in love
かなりモーレツにピチピチよん
Quite fiercely in the prime of youth
でもサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
But Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday, solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ Mine
I love it all, I love it all, I love it all, mine
あ もうムリ 終わり 鬱 全然かわいくないしさ
Ah, no more, it's over, depression. I'm not cute at all, and...
めんどーくさいよね？ はー消えたい 消えよ
I'm such a hassle, right? *Sigh* I wanna disappear. I will.
(そこがいい！) そこがいい？ (そこがいい！)
(That's what's great!) That's what's great? (That's what's great!)
ウソばっか (いい女！) いい女？ (いい女！)
Total lies. (Fine woman!) Fine woman? (Fine woman!)
本当に？ (お宝以上！) お宝以上？ (お宝以上！)
Really? (Better than treasure!) Better than treasure? (Better than treasure!)
そうかな～ (最後のヒロイン！) 最後のヒロイン？ (最後のヒロイン！)
You think so~? (The ultimate heroine!) The ultimate heroine? (The ultimate heroine!)
そうかにゃあ？
Is that so, meow?
弱気バイバイ スタコラサッサ
Timidity bye-bye, scurrying away!
そそそそうかもね そうだよね！
Y-Y-Y-Yeah, maybe so! That's right!
にゃーんか元気になってきた！
Sometheeeng's got me feeling energized!
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ごめんねキッス
Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday, sorry-kiss!
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ
I love everything, I love everything, I love everything
私が瞬くたび 鳴り響く効果音
Every time I blink, a sound effect rings out
きゃぴ
Kyapi!
Kyapi
洗脳してあげる 洗脳してあげる
I'll brainwash you, I'll brainwash you
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up! Forever seventeen
接近して感電中 ズッキュンしてバタンキュー
Closing in, getting shocked, shot through the heart, down for the count
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up! 萌えよSeventeen
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up! Moe on, seventeen!
セクシー×4 破廉恥バンビーナ
Sexy x4, shameless Bambina
洗脳してあげる ×××してあげない
I'll brainwash you, I won't do XXX for you
カワイイ？ 顔がいい？ 気持ちがイイ！
Cute? Good-looking? It feels so good!
洗脳シテアゲル アゲル アゲル
I'll brainwash you, I'll do it, I'll do it
もっとアイドルでいさせてよ
Let me be an idol even more
きゃぴ
Kyapi!
きゃぴきゃぴ
Kyapi-kyapi
いくつになっても
No matter how old I get...
きゃきゃきゃきゃきゃきゃきゃきゃきゃ……きゃぴ
Kya-kya-kya-kya-kya-kya-kya-kya... Kyapi!
(1 & 2 & 3 & 4) Mixer! Mixer!
きゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅ……きゅるりん
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu... Kyururin!
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ 発散中
I love everything, I love everything, I love everything, radiating it out
なんてったってなんてったってなんてったってヘヴィキュート
After all, after all, after all, heavy cute
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ 愛罠罠罠罠
I love everything, I love everything, love trap-trap-trap-trap
来世も来々世も浮気しちゃダメよ
You can't cheat on me in the next life or the one after that!
きゃぴ
Kyapi!
洗脳してあげる 洗脳してあげる
I'll brainwash you, I'll brainwash you
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up! Forever seventeen
監視して催眠中 ズッキュンしてLovin' You
Watching you, hypnotizing you, shot through the heart, lovin' you
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up! 萌えよSeventeen
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up! Moe on, seventeen!
セクシー×4 ごめんね マイダーリン
Sexy x4, sorry, my darling
洗脳してあげる もういっそ産んであげる
I'll brainwash you, I might as well give birth to you
カワイイ？ 顔がいい？ 気持ちがイイ！
Cute? Good-looking? It feels so good!
洗脳シテアゲル アゲルッタラ ア・ゲ・ル！
I'll brainwash you, I said I will, I! Will!
もっとI wanna beat you up!
More, I wanna beat you up!
きっと恋するだっちゃ
You're sure to fall in love-daccha!
ずっとアイドルでいさせてね
Let me be an idol forever, okay?
神様お願い きゃぴ
God, please! Kyapi!
(ヤババババ 脳Shake it! Shake it!)
(Crazy-crazy, brain shake it! Shake it!)
きゃぴのびのび
Kyapi, carefree and easy
君たちー！ マリンの7周年ライブを見てくれて、ありがとうございましたー！
Everyone! Thank you so much for watching Marine's 7th Anniversary Live!
今お披露目した新曲の「きゃぴ」は、配信終了後アニメMVが公開されます！
For the new song "Kyapi" that I just premiered, an animated MV will be released right after this stream!
マリンの考える、一味とマリンの関係性とイチャイチャが詰まったMVなので、
It's an MV packed with Marine's take on the relationship and flirting between Ichimi and Marine,
いっぱい見て、いっぱい一緒にキュンキュンしてほしいです！
so I hope you watch it a lot and let your hearts flutter together!
見てるうちに、曲が頭から離れなくなります。洗脳させてくださーい！
As you keep watching, the song won't leave your head. Please let me brainwash you!
続いて、7周年記念グッズのお知らせでーす！
Next up, here are the announcements for the 7th Anniversary Commemorative Goods!
まずは、B2タペストリー！ こちらは、今回の新衣装の水着姿をあかさあい先生に描き下ろしていただきましたー！
First is the B2 Tapestry! Akasa Ai-sensei drew an exclusive illustration of my new swimsuit outfit for this!
超美しい！ 肉感がすごーい！ 絶対飾ってくださいね！
It's super beautiful! The voluptuousness is amazing! Please be sure to display it!
続いて、船長描き下ろしのランダムラバーキーホルダー！
Next, the Random Rubber Keychain drawn by Senchou!
デフォルメの絵柄を模索して、「これだ！」と思えるデフォルメにたどり着いたので、こんな感じで描いてみましたー！
I explored various chibi styles until I arrived at one where I thought, "This is it!", and drew them like this!
新衣装と、まだラバーキーホルダー描いてないなっていう衣装でまとめてみましたー！
I put together the new outfit along with outfits that haven't been made into rubber keychains yet!
かなり可愛いバランスになったかなって自信作なので、絶対ゲットしてくださいね！
I'm confident the proportions turned out super cute, so definitely be sure to get them!
続いてはこちら！ ぬいぐるみキーホルダー くらげ風水着衣装ver.！
Next up is this! The Plush Keychain: Jellyfish Swimsuit Outfit ver.!
今回の新衣装のデザインで、ちっちゃくて可愛いぬいぐるみです！
It's a tiny and cute plushie featuring the design of my new outfit!
お写真を撮った時に楽しげに見えるように、めっちゃテンション高い顔に船長が描き下ろしました！
Senchou drew this super high-energy expression so it looks cheerful when you take photos with it!
楽しいひと時のオトモにしてねー！
Please make it your companion for fun times!
続いてはこちら！ 2way推し事バッグ！
Next up is this! The 2-Way Oshi Bag!
船長の新衣装の太ももにつけているポーチのデザインとお揃いです！
It matches the design of the pouch on Senchou's thigh from the new outfit!
普段使いしやすく、推し活のときには推し活仕様にできるというところを意識しました！
I made sure it's easy for everyday use, while easily customizable for fan activities when you go out!
シックなデザインなので、これなら日常使いできますよねー！
It's a chic design, so you can definitely use it everyday!
そして、マリンとドキドキ海水浴っていう、ちょっとラブラブなASMRボイスもあります！
And we also have an ASMR voice pack, "Heart-Pounding Beach Trip with Marine," which is a bit lovey-dovey!
ちょっとグイグイいかせてもらうんで、覚悟の準備をしておいてくださーい！
I'm going to be pretty assertive, so please prepare yourselves!
そしてそして、フルセット購入特典は、チケット風カード！
And also, the full set purchase bonus is a Ticket-Style Card!
昨日ね、夏の野外フェスに出演したところなので、ちょっと意識してサマーフェスチケット風でーす！
Since I just performed at an outdoor summer festival yesterday, I themed it after a summer festival ticket!
数量限定バージョンは直筆メッセージ入り、通常バージョンは複製直筆メッセージ入りです！
The limited-quantity version includes a handwritten message, and the regular version has a printed handwritten message!
記念にぜひぜひゲットしてくださーい！
Please be sure to get it to commemorate the occasion!
そしてこの後は、メンバーシップ限定で水着の撮影会を行いまーす！
And after this, we'll be holding a swimsuit photoshoot session exclusively for members!
色んな差分をお見せするので、いっぱい堪能してくださいねー！
I'll show you various outfit variations, so please enjoy them to your heart's content!
マリンのメン限は激甘らしいので、
I hear Marine's member-only streams are super sweet,
これを機にぜひ他のメン限アーカイブと合わせてメンバーシップいかがでしょうかー！
so how about joining the membership to enjoy all the other member archives too?!
また後日、振り返り配信で今日のいろんな裏話を聞いてくださーい！
Also, in a recap stream at a later date, please come hear all the behind-the-scenes stories from today!
それでは行きますよー、出航ー！
Here we go then... Set sail!
ああー
Ah...